Farsas Castle    Oscar's Residence
Erase the words to be
torn asunder at the root.
Rid all meaning from the
rain that takes shape.
Let all cycles return as cycles.
Abide by my laws, all that may arise.
Are you done?
Yes.
This should negate all external attacks,
be they physical or magical.
As long as I remain alive,
no other human can break this spell.
Sounds like practically cheating.
You made a contract with a witch.
This is the least I could do.
That said, you're still vulnerable
to poison and psychological attacks.
So do be careful.
Not too shabby for an apprentice mage.
That's my cover story within the palace.
However, I left the tower to lift
your curse, as your protector.
Don't forget that.
All I want is for you to marry me.
You know I said "no," right?
~ The Past Recalled Once Again ~
Finding a successor sounds
like a real problem.
Isn't there anyone else
who's part of the royal bloodline?
I seem to recall there
being a few branch families.
About fifteen years ago,
there was a series of cases where babies
disappeared around the kingdom.
Fifteen years ago, you say...
It was then that His Highness's
cousins all went missing.
As a result, there aren't any royals left
who are younger than he is.
There.
Kav     Farsas Mage
Sylvia, how are you faring?
Sylvia     Farsas Mage
I've almost got it.
What?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
She did that without an incantation?
That's...
Miss Tinasha, was it?
Yeah.
His Highness brought her
from the witch's tower.
Witch's tower?
Huh...
Sorry to interrupt your rest.
You really helped me out.
Pay it no mind.
I'm always happy to do this much.
A sparring match?
General Als and Meredina, looks like.
He's quite the fighter.
He's one of the younger generals,
but the most skilled of them all.
Though His Highness is
stronger than General Als.
Ugh...
What's with that reaction?
Oh, don't mind me.
No wonder he conquered the tower.
Where are you going?
Some sword practice sounds nice
about now, after so long.
I see.
What?
Let's go again.
You seem too good to be just a dabbler.
If you joined us instead of being a mage,
you'd fit in just fine.
Thanks for the kind words.
Well? How was she?
You saw for yourself.
Meredina     Farsas Officer                                           Als      Farsas General
She's obviously more than just
His Highness's prize pet.
I heard she's the pupil of a witch.
Is this really okay?
Jealousy doesn't suit you, Meredina.
Ow, ow, ow!
Master.
Litola. You were here?
I'm glad to see you're well.
You've found a fine individual, it seems.
You think?
You seem to be enjoying
yourself much more now.
I guess you could say that...
Well, it's not bad.
So?
Yes.
There's something I thought you should know.
Is that you, Tinasha?
Did you get a good work...
out...
What happened?
Why are you dressed like that?
I'll be leaving for two or three days.
Hold on, now.
Where are you going?
I'm free to go where I want.
I'll make sure I come back.
I formed a contract with you.
I can't have you leaving at any time.
At least tell me where you're headed.
The magical lake in Druza.
The magical lake?!
That's dangerous!
That's where the demonic beast
was sealed away seventy years ago!
There are large surges of
high magical power occurring there.
I'm off to find out who's responsible
and what they're plotting.
In that case, I'll join you.
That won't be necessary.
The crown prince shouldn't venture out, anyway.
That land is effectively
under Farsas jurisdiction.
Even with my word, the state won't
take kindly to you investigating alone.
If the two of us go, it might
become an even bigger problem.
I'll gather able soldiers.
I'm not obligated to protect
anyone other than you.
I'm well aware.
One hour.
I won't wait any longer.
What do you expect to find out here, Valt?
Nothing visible to the naked eye.
But it's about to begin.
She should take notice pretty soon.
The Witch of the Azure Moon?
Will she really come all this way?
Yes, she will.
She has eyes all across the mainland.
After all, she's looking for him as well.
Is everyone ready?
Is that a dragon you have on your shoulder?
What?
My name is Sylvia.
We haven't spoken, have we?
It's a pleasure!
Y-Yes.
How amazing.
It's my first time seeing one!
Th... There, there...
I-I'm sorry!
It's not used to people, so please be careful.
Tinasha.
What's that thing?
I was going to ride it if I was going alone.
It doesn't look big enough to ride.
We're embarking on a survey
of the magical lake in Druza.
We don't know
what we'll find, so stay vigilant.
Also, don't go against her orders.
Is it really okay to say that?
Yeah.
You really are a strange man.
It's fine.
I'll take care of it.
Let's go!
Off we go, Tinasha.
Like dust in the wind,
no one back then is still alive.
And so, everything I know leaves me behind.
Still, I remain in the same place.
This is the path I chose for myself.
Let's go, Tinasha.
Hey, what's wrong?
Is something the matter?
No, it's nothing.
Ynureid Fortress    Northwestern Farsas, Bordering Druza
Your Highness, look at that.
Yeah.
Let's go!
Yes!
Seventy years ago, the neighboring
nation of Druza invaded Farsas.
As Farsas drove back the enemy
with a steady army,
Druza unleashed their giant
magic weapon, a demonic beast.
The beast, not fully
under control, was let loose,
laying waste to foes,
allies, and the land itself.
Ultimately, the beast was sealed away
by the Witch of the Azure Moon,
but its miasma poisoned the earth,
turning it into a barren
wasteland devoid of any life.
What a sight to behold.
It's a nightmare come to life.
This is where that demonic beast is sealed?
It was a formidable opponent.
With humans in the area, it was
all I could do to seal it away.
If I had kept on fighting back then,
the outcome would have
been much more gruesome.
Tinasha?
I know you're there.
Stop hiding and show yourself.
Long time no see.
You're...
I didn't think I'd live to see you again.
Druza Mage
Your dress, your beauty...
It's like I've been
transported back seventy years,
Miss Witch of the Azure Moon.
A witch?!
Miss Tinasha?
And you've grown quite old yourself.
Or should I say you've shriveled up?
Back then, you were just a child.
I would normally have been long dead by now.
You see, we're not all like you.
I see you've taken after your master
in the way you look and talk.
You mean the master who you beheaded?
I'm very pleased to hear that.
I'll do you a favor, then.
You can share the same fate.
Oh, how terrifying.
I'm not powerful enough to
handle you, so I'll take my leave.
I suggest that all of you
depart this place, too.
Or perhaps you need to be
convinced with a death or two.
Stand back!
Why, you!
Your Highness!
Are you okay?
Yes.
Tinasha.
He got away.
You know him?
He was one of Druza's mages
controlling the beast.
So that surge of magical power...
Most likely, it's the result
of trying to revive the beast.
Revenge after seventy years, huh?
I believe so.
Some first-aid treatment.
Miss Tinasha, you're a witch?
By the way, did you let your arm
take the hit on purpose?
Attacks don't affect me, do they?
I'm sorry I kept it a secret.
I didn't want to startle anyone.
That's not it! I...
You mustn't.
Witches are objects of fear.
Don't feel bad.
Let's retreat for now.
We'll gather forces and arm ourselves.
I'll go after that mage.
You can't be serious.
Now that we're onto them, they'll try to
undo the seal as fast as they can.
I'm coming with you.
Again?
I know you're very capable,
and I admire your willingness.
But if you're going to become king,
you need to learn to delegate.
I understand.
But not now.
I won't have you do all the dirty work for me.
Isn't that why you dragged me out of my tower?
No.
Their target is Farsas.
I can't have you bear that burden alone.
I swear.
You really are so stubborn.
Our contract is only for one year.
Feel free to have me solve
your troubles while I'm here.
Tinasha.
Besides, the weight of your
burdens is nothing to me.
Oscar.
You and I are bound by our contract,
and as long as I am your protector,
I will always return to you,
no matter what I do or where I go.
And I won't die before you do.
That's for certain.
I understand. Go on.
Yes.
Nark.
Tinasha, when you come back...
Yeah?
We should get married.
N-Not happening!
Don't jinx yourself like that!
Hurry and break the final seal!
We don't have time!
The control spell isn't fully ready yet!
I don't care!
The witch found us!
The witch?!
No way...
Hurry!
Break the seal on the beast
before they storm in here!
Begone, definiens!
It's not too late.
I'll make sure power is restored to Druza,
with help from the demonic beast!
I won't let it end
now that we've come this far!
Looks like I missed one.
What's wrong?
You want to undo the seal?
I'll break it for you, then.
As it stands, I can't lay
a finger on it, either.
Sing for me, ancient forewarning.
Chains born in days bygone,
crumble by my command.
It's dangerous.
Stay away until it's all over.
It's been seventy years.
Did you have a pleasant slumber?
That's one bushy mane.
Brim forth, my definition!
Burst!
It heals as fast as ever.
However...
Rise up.
The cage that confines you
hides yet in darkness.
Your view shows naught
but these seven shackles.
Tranquility is blind without meaning.
Slumber in the cave of ignorance you rejected.
Sorry, but this time, you must die.
You have nothing to gain from living here.
Recognize my will as command.
Silence brimming in ubiquity.
You hold no power without my words.
Define the light that extinguishes.
This is the end!
Tinasha?
Someone call for a mage!
You may enter.
Pardon me.
How's Tinasha?
I've performed a full body examination.
I couldn't find any severe wounds.
No wounds?
What about her stomach?
It looks like she patched herself up.
I can't tell how it looks on the inside.
I see.
Can I go check up on her?
Go ahead.
I can't imagine she'll come to until she's
recovered her magical power, though.
Tinasha. Are you awak—
Tinasha?
Don't come in while I'm naked!
I had suffered severe organ damage,
so I recovered by accelerating
my bodily growth.
Organ damage?
Are you okay?
I'm all better now.
Just a little anemic from all the bleeding.
Will your appearance change back?
No, it won't.
My appearance was due to halting my growth.
You really defeated the demonic beast, huh?
Piece of cake.
What about that deadly injury?
You saved us.
Your actions meant no one else was harmed.
Thank you.
This is the least I could do.
I'm a witch, after all.
~ What the Forest Dreams Of ~